（探照灯影业）
♪ 今晚你属于我 ♪
♪ Tonight you're mine completely ♪
♪ 你把爱给得温柔如蜜 ♪
♪ You give your love so sweetly ♪
♪ 今夜你眼里有爱的光辉 ♪
♪ Tonight the light of love is in your eyes ♪
♪ 但明天你还会爱我吗？ ♪
♪ Will you still love me tomorrow? ♪
请稍等...
One minute...
快派个人去那里
Get somebody down there
女士 您还好吗？
Ma'am, are you okay?
您能听见我说话吗？
Can you hear me?
南草坪上有人受伤
I got someone on the south lawn,
我们需要急救人员立刻过来
we need paramedics over here right away
收到
Copy that.
天呐 你这是怎么了？
Jesus Christ, what happened to you?
- 婆家 - 你说是婆家吗？
- In-laws. Did you say in-laws?
你的婆家怎么了？女士
What about your in-laws, ma'am?
嘿 嘿 嘿 别昏过去
Hey, hey, hey, stay with us.
睁眼看着我
Just keep your eyes on me.
放松
Take it easy.
慢慢呼吸
Slow, steady breaths.
哇 哇 哇
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
她倒下了
She's down!
把担架抬过来
Get that stretcher over here!
先把她抬上去 数到三一起抬
Get her loaded up. On my count, one hand down.
情况危急
Critical condition.
准备好了吗？
Ready?
一 二 三
One, two, three!
一 二 抬
One, two... Up!
挺住
Stay with us.
她还活着么？
She in?
是
Yeah.
给她测一下生命体征
Let's get a set of vitals on her.
我这就给她接氧气
I'm gonna get oxygen on.
氧气面罩已戴好
Mask's on
我要检查一下瞳孔
I'm gonna check pupils.
体位性低血压
Orthostatic.
血压测不出
I don't have a pressure.
瞳孔无反应
No pupil response.
检测脉搏
Let's check her pulse.
无脉博
No pulse.
她发生了心脏骤停
She's in cardiac arrest.
开始胸外按压
Starting compressions.
充电中
Charging.
200焦耳
Two hundred.
准备
Ready.
清场
Clear.
正在运送一名体位性低血压的白人女性
Ortho coming in with a Caucasian female.
年龄在二十五岁左右
Mid to late twenties.
处于严重休克状态
In severe shock.
多处撕裂伤
Multiple lacerations.
左手中可能有枪伤
Possible gunshot wound through the left hand.
子弹贯穿
Through and through.
脉搏？
Pulse.
无脉博
No pulse.
我这就继续做胸外按压
I'll get her compressions again.
充电中
Charging.
200焦耳
Two hundred.
清场
Clear.
- 捉迷藏？ - 逮到她了
- Hide and seek？ - She's here!
我来帮你检测
I'll test you.
三 二 一
Three, two, one.
你会明白的
You'll see
《准备好了没：2度开局》
字幕贡献者
pubuqi（subhd.tv）
Borcolasky（subhd.tv）
小p（蒙太奇字幕组）
勒多马斯太太？
Mrs. Le Domas?
我在哪里？
Where am I?
您现在位于康涅狄格州的伍德伯里
You're in Woodbury, Connecticut.
圣约翰医院
St. John's Hospital.
为什么给我戴手铐
Why am I handcuffed?
- 勒多马斯夫人 - 叫我麦考利小姐
- Mrs. Le Domas. - It's Ms. MacCaullay.
这里写着您嫁给了亚历克斯·勒多马斯
It says here you married an Alex Le Domas.
那段婚姻没能维持下去
It didn't work out.
我是罗杰·巴塞特警探
I'm Detective Roger Bassett.
你有麻烦了 麦考利女士
You're in some trouble, Ms. MacCaullay.
你现已被伍德伯里警察局拘留
You're being detained by the Woodbury Police Department.
涉嫌纵火和谋杀
Under suspicion of arson and murder.
扑灭大火后 他们在屋内发现了
They found the remains of two people in the house
两具遗体
after they put out the fire.
你的衣服上沾满了鲜血
And your clothes were drenched in blood.
并且那不是你的血
It wasn't yours.
如果你愿意做个陈述
Now, if you'd care to make a statement.
能给我支烟吗
Could you pass me a cigarette?
麦考利女士 这对你可没什么好处
This is not going to go well for you, Ms. MacCaullay.
只要你配合 事情会好办很多
Things would go a lot easier if you would just cooperate.
有人来看她
She has a visitor.
你在等人吗？
Are you expecting someone?
哦 天呐
Oh, shit.
看看你
Look at you.
你来这里干什么？
What are you doing here?
嗯 我还是你的紧急联系人
Well, I'm still your emergency contact.
谢了
So, thanks for that.
你是谁？
Who are you?
费丝·麦考利
Faith MacCaullay.
你又是谁？
Who are you?
一家人？
Family?
生物学意义上 对 我们是姐妹
Biologically speaking, yeah, we're sisters,
但我们不是一家人
but we're not family.
好吧
Okay.
我会给你们几分钟时间
I'm going to give you a few minutes.
然后我会带你去警局
Then I'm going to take you to the station.
做陈述
Get that statement.
发生什么事了？
What happened?
你不会信的
You wouldn't believe me.
这话可能没错 但我大老远开车
That's probably true, but I drove all
来到康涅狄格这个鬼地方
the way out to bumfuck Connecticut,
- 所以... - 你从哪儿来的？
- so... - Where'd you come from?
你的意思是我住在哪里吗？
You mean, where do I live?
是的
Sure.
默里山
Murray Hill.
我现在在切尔西
I'm in Chelsea.
酷
Yeah, cool.
你在纽约住了多久了
How long have you lived in New York?
我十八岁时搬过去的
I moved out there when I was 18.
就像你一样
Just like you.
- 你竟然从没想过... - 格蕾丝 得了吧
- And you never thought... - Grace, come on.
很久以前你就说得很清楚了
You made it very clear a long time ago that
你不想做我的姐姐 好吗？
you're not interested in being my sister, okay?
我也是这么想的
And the feeling's mutual.
我来这里不是为了重聚
I'm not here for a reunion.
好 见到你我也很高兴
Yeah, it's good to see you, too.
你好吗？
How are you?
- 我他妈好极了 - 是吗？
- I'm fucking amazing. - Yeah?
真好极了
Yeah, really good.
我现在做自媒体
I'm a social media coordinator.
我住在一间超棒的一居室里
I live in a kick-ass one bedroom and
还有个帅得要命的男朋友 叫德里克
I have a hot-as-fuck boyfriend named Derek.
而且我不用靠跟你的亚历克斯·勒多马斯上床来得到这些
And I didn't have to fuck Alex Le Domas to get it.
全靠我自己的努力
I did it all by myself.
你怎么知道亚历克斯
How do you know about Alex?
有一次我在第七大道二十五街的
I saw you together once at
全食超市看到你们在一起
the Whole Foods on 25th and 7th.
他很高
He's tall.
你本可以打个招呼的
You could have said something.
为什么？
Why?
我活的那么好
I'm in a good place.
干嘛去见你这个唠叨鬼
You're a negative person.
我才不是唠叨鬼
I'm not a negative person.
- 尽管你抛弃了我 - 我没有抛弃你
- And even though you abandoned me... - I did not abandon you.
我依然相信人性的善良
I still believe in the fundamental goodness of humanity.
天呐 如果你知道我刚才经历了什么...
Oh my God, if you knew what I'd just been through...
那就告诉我吧
Then tell me.
我说过 你不会相信的
I told you you wouldn't believe me.
好 你没事就好
Alright, I'm glad you're okay.
还是这个苦瓜脸
But you haven't changed.
那我走
I'm just gonna go.
费丝 等一下
Faith, wait.
婚礼结束后 亚历克斯告诉我 我得抽一张牌
After the wedding, Alex tells me I have to pull a card.
玩上面写的任何游戏
Play whatever game it says.
某种...
Some kind of
入会仪式
initiation ritual.
我起初觉得挺奇怪
Which I thought was weird.
但我想让他们喜欢我
But I wanted them to like me
毕竟他们要成为我的新家人了
because they were gonna be my new family.
总之
Anyway...
我抽到了捉迷藏
I pull hide and seek.
然后 周围人立马安静了
And it gets real quiet.
显然
Because apparently...
那是一张坏牌
That's the bad card.
他们以为必须把我献祭给魔鬼
And they think they have to try to sacrifice me to the devil.
他们告诉我 有机会赢
They told me I could win.
如果我能躲到天亮
If I stayed hidden till dawn.
但他们认为
But they thought...
如果我赢的话
If I won...
他们会死
They'd die.
然后他们开始猎杀我
So they hunted me.
我
I got...
手中枪了
Shot through the hand.
被一个管家打得半死
Beat to shit by a butler.
并且我的
And my...
我的丈夫 刺伤了我
My husband... Stabbed me.
但是我撑到了天亮
But I made it till dawn.
我他妈赢了
I fucking won.
所以
So...
他们死了吗？
Did they drop dead?
不
No.
他们爆炸了
They blew up.
爆炸了？
在他们爆炸后 有个男人坐在椅子上
And then after they blew up, there was a guy in a chair.
他朝我点了点头
And he nodded at me.
椅子上的男人是谁？
Who was the guy in the chair?
我不知道
I don't know.
虽然他是透明的 但我非常确定他是...
But he was see-through, so I'm pretty sure he was...
你懂的...
You know...
你肯定要进监狱了
You are so going to jail.
是的
Yeah.
（战事陷入胶着 结束遥遥无期）
批准停火
Approve the ceasefire.
（突发新闻 双方同意停火）
早上好 丹福斯先生
Good morning, Mr. Danforth.
好久不见
It's been a long time.
我有些消息
I have some news.
出去
Leave us.
勒多马斯家族没了
The Le Domases are no more.
佩妮拉
Pernilla.
你能把我的孩子叫来吗？
Can you find my children?
当然
Of course.
我转告其他人
I'll inform the others.
（今晚有好戏了）
（新娘活下来了 勒多马斯家族失败了 游戏继续）
喂
Hello.
马上把我的律师都叫来
Get all my lawyers here right now.
马上
Right away.
（进击工作室）
历经岁月沧桑的古老宅邸合集
The collection of the weathered houses.
克洛特恩堡 夏洛特
Clothurnburg. Charlotte.
（西班牙语）别弄他妈的头发了 卡门
¡Deja el puto pelo, Carmen!
（西班牙语）操
¡Coño!
这破玩意谁写的
Who wrote this shit?
我就即兴发挥吧
I'll just wing it.
我按自己的方式来
I'll do my own thing.
像往常一样
Like always.
（西班牙语）真见鬼
¡Puta madre!
（西班牙语）真是他妈的大好事
¡Me cago en esta puta!
（西班牙语）过来 卡蒂亚
¡Ven ya, Katia!
（西班牙语）哦 天呐
¡Ay, Dios!
嘿 好了
Hey, all right.
告诉威廉 那人搞砸了
Tell William the guy shot the jet.
（鲜肉公司）
轮到我了 混蛋
It's my time, motherfucker.
本森
Benson.
把我的刀给我
Bring me my knife!
这是我们的机会
This is our chance!
勒拜尔万岁
Le Bail be praised!
耶
Yeah!
开干
Shot!
（丹福斯）
父亲
Father
所以勒多马斯家族失败了
So the Le Domas failed.
新娘活下来了
The bride survived.
游戏继续
The ball is in play.
不
No.
那不公平
That's not fair.
这是我们的
It's... it's ours!
没关系
It doesn't matter.
规则就是这样
It's in the rules.
你们知道该做什么了吧
You know what you have to do.
爸
Dad.
求你了
Please.
像个爷们
Be a fucking man!
别忘了你姓丹福斯
You're a Danforth.
这绝不能离开我们家族
This... must never leave our family.
你必须夺回这个席位
You must win the seat back.
我们会的
We will.
我保证
You have my word.
好吧...
Well...
痛快点吧
Get on with it.
泰特斯
Titus.
结束了
It's over.
对新娘来说还没结束
Not for the bride.
好了 麦考利夫人
All right, Mrs. MacCaullay.
我们给你拿些衣服
We'll get you some clothes.
然后我们到警局继续谈话
Then continue our conversation at the station.
我迫不及待想听你讲那只山羊的事
I can't wait for you to tell me about that goat...
这一切都会是你的
It's all gonna be yours.
去他妈的规则
Fuck the rules!
求你了 求您了
Please, please.
勒多马斯夫人
Mrs. Le Domas!
这他妈什么情况
What is going on
这事怎么又开始了
This can't be happening again
听着 我得有武器
Listen, I need a weapon.
我先回车里拿
I'm going back to the car.
别抛弃我
Do not leave me
好的 好的
Okay, Okay
你伤到我了
You hurting me!
你现在的捉迷藏水平也不咋样嘛
Not so good at hide and seek now!
哦天呐 搞毛线啊
Oh my God! What the fuck!
好了
Okay.
可能还有更多的人来
There could be more coming.
我得把手铐弄开
I gotta get out of these cuffs.
还好吗？
Okay?
搞什么鬼
What the fuck?
我们得赶紧走
We gotta get out of here and disappear.
你他妈在干什么？
What the fuck are you doing?
我们可能需要打架
We might have to fight.
穿着病号服我没法打架
I can't fight in this gown.
没时间找新衣服了
No time to look for new clothes.
你还要打架？
You have to fight?
好的 好的
Okay, okay.
快点 我们得走了
Come on, we gotta go.
真是个乱摊子
What a mess.
威尔金森先生显然想
Looks like Mr. Wilkinson tried to.
在游戏开始前就杀了女孩
Killed the girl before the game could begin.
并让他的整个血脉过早地走向灭亡
And condemned his entire bloodline to a premature end.
嗯 这就是违反拉贝尔先生规则的下场
Well, that's what happens when you break one of Mr. LaBelle's rules.
你好
Hello there.
请问你是谁？
And who might you be?
就在那一刻 我知道我们俩都会挺过去的
And right then I knew that we were both going to make it.
因为我们有这一刻值得为之而活
Because we had this moment to live for.
而如今 我们就在这里
And here we are.
我们做到了
We made it.
我爱你
I love you so much.
马克
Mark.
那天我们在化疗病房相遇
When we met that day in the chemo ward.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen.
我非常抱歉地告诉你们
I am terribly sorry to tell you but I'm going
我不得不请你们所有人离开这里
to have to ask you all to vacate the premises.
不幸的是 我们出现了煤气泄漏
Unfortunately, we have a gas leak.
你他妈在开玩笑吗？
Are you fucking kidding me?
她没有
She's not.
请你赶紧滚出去
Kindly get the fuck out.
此外请你礼貌点
Besides, you could do way better.
各位请注意
Attention ladies and gentlemen.
请根据指示...
do on procedures...
这些人该回家了
These people need to go home.
滚出去
Get the fuck out.
你为什么总觉得非得当个混蛋不可？
Why do you always feel the need to be such a dick?
你但凡有点善意都意义非凡
Your little grace goes a long way.
好吧 那很可笑
Well, that was funny.
今天不是搞笑的日子
Today is not the day for funny.
爸爸给我们一个任务 我不会让他失望
Dad gave us a mission and I'm not going to let him down.
呦
Yo!
表亲们
Cousins!
已经过去多久了？
How long has it been?
我先报个名
I'm gonna sign it up.
好戏开场时来叫我
Come get me when the fireworks start.
摸你鸡鸡
Dick tap!
你不必跟他说话
You don't have to speak to him.
别惹事 行吗？
Just don't start anything, okay?
今天别惹事
Not today.
该死的基普
Fucking Kip.
我们非做不可
It had to be done.
你伤心的时候看起来真像他
You look just like him when you're sad.
我再说一遍 请保持冷静 有序地走向出口
I'll repeat, please remain calm and proceed to the exits in an orderly fashion.
女士们先生们 收拾好你们的破烂 滚出去
Ladies and gentlemen, pack up your shit and get the fuck out.
请快点
Please.
委员会上次举行现场会议是什么时候？
When was the last time the council actually convened in person?
1963年10月
October, 1963.
我查过了
I looked it up.
嗯 他们现在正前往小屋的路上
Well, they're on their way to the lodge now.
开始了
And so it begins.
哦 天呐
Oh, man.
是啊
Yeah.
伊格纳西奥
Ignacio.
费利佩
Felipe.
早上好 丹福斯夫人
Buenos Días, Senora Danforth.
你一点没老
You haven't aged a day.
弗朗西丝卡没来吗？
No Francesca?
我原本以为她肯定想亲眼见证这一刻
I thought for sure she'd want to be here for this.
她马上就来 相信我
She'll be along, believe me.
她不会错过这个的
She wouldn't miss this for the world.
真是件好事
It's exciting...
嗯 对我来说真是件好事
it's exciting for me.
对你来说不是
It's terrifying for you.
对 还有你
Yes, and you.
走吧 费利佩
Vamos, Felipe.
乌苏拉
Ursula.
泰特斯
Titus.
你还记得我儿子吗？承福
You remember my son? Cheng Fu
认识你承福 欢迎
I know you, Chengfu. Welcome.
Wi-Fi密码是什么？
What's the Wi-Fi password?
态度好点儿
Be nice
马杜
Madhu
维拉杰
Viraj
玛蒂娜 欢迎
Martina, welcome.
规则是什么？
So how's this shit work?
大家马上到齐了 到时候律师会向大家说明一切
Our guests will be arriving soon, and then the lawyer will explain everything.
啊 大律师
Ah, lawyer.
跟这边这位漂亮笨蛋说话慢点
Speak slow for this beautiful dum-dum over here.
爆破音
Single-syllable words.
看来我们的贵宾要到了
It appears our guest of honor is arriving.
你好 格蕾丝
Hello, Grace.
我是乌苏拉·丹福斯
I'm Ursula Danforth.
这是我哥哥泰特斯
This is my brother Titus.
欢迎来到我们家
Welcome to our home.
父亲 我可以跟她说话吗
May I speak to her, Father?
（西班牙语）可以 可以 去吧 费利佩
Sí, sí, ándale, Felipe.
它伤不着你
It can't hurt you.
你见到勒贝尔先生了吗？
Did you see Mr. LeBail?
等一下
One second.
在开始之前 我得先拍张自拍
I just gotta take a quick selfie before we start.
呦
Yo!
这女孩打败了勒多马斯家族
This girl bested the Le Domases.
还有比尔·威尔金森
And Bill Wilkinson.
我们能开始了吗？
Can we start this, please?
切斯特他妈在哪儿？
And where the fuck is Chester?
我们的父亲...去世了
Our father... passed.
搞什么
What the fuck?
什么？
What?
昨晚 在睡梦中
Last night, in his sleep.
等等 等等
Wait, wait, wait.
那意味着你现在要参赛了
So does that mean that you're playing now?
既然我们是双胞胎 那我们俩都会上场 对吧？
As we are twins, we will both be taking the field, yes?
搞什么鬼？
What the fuck?
不
No.
多方便啊
How convenient.
（西班牙语）我早就跟你说过 丹福斯一家都是阴险小人
Te dije que los Danforths son unas víboras.
（西班牙语）没事的
Está bien.
（西班牙语）他们在耍诡计
Y que iban a hacer trampas.
（西班牙语）行了 别担心
Ya, no te preocupes
格蕾丝 我明白这对你来说一定很可怕
Grace, I realize this must be terrifying for you.
但你来到这里 是因为一个非常特别
But you are here for a very special,
非常令人兴奋的原因
very exciting reason.
勒多马斯夫人 您可真是掀起了不小的风波
You've caused quite a stir, Mrs. Le Domas.
我叫麦考利
MacCaullay!
我是拉贝尔先生和拉贝尔组织的唯一律师
I am the sole attorney for Mr. LaBelle and the LaBelle organization.
该组织由一个理事会领导 该理事会由六个家族的首领组成
The organization is led by a council made up of the heads of six families,
包括你的婆家
including your in-laws.
现在德莫斯和威尔金森家族已经被消灭
Now The DeMoss and Wilkinson families have been wiped out.
六大家族议会目前缩减到四个
The council of six families is currently down to four.
你在这里的原因是
The reason you're here is
你从勒德莫斯家的捉迷藏游戏中幸存下来
that by surviving Le DeMoss' game of hide and seek,
你触发了我们组织章程中一条
you triggered a very seldom use
极少被援引的条款
clause in our organization's bylaws.
要知道 在理事会中
You see, on the council there is
有一个席位的权力比其他席位更大
one seat with more power than the others.
至高席位
The high seat.
它配有这个权力徽章
And it comes with this, sigil of power.
直到现在 那个席位由切斯特·丹福斯占据
Until now, that seat was occupied by Chester Danforth.
我想你听说过他
I presume you've heard of him.
因为你触发了那个条款 至高席位现在空缺了
Because you triggered that clause, the high seat is
很多很多年来的第一次
now vacant for the first time in many, many years.
而且 信不信由你
And, believe it or not,
你获得了一个赢得至高席位的机会
you've been given an opportunity to win the high seat.
能从游戏中幸存下来的人非常少
It's very rare that someone survives a game,
所以会获得这份奖励
so it comes with this reward.
其余议会家族的首领们
And the heads of the remaining council families
也会竭力争夺这个席位
will try to win the seat for themselves.
或者就我们而言 夺回本应属于我们的东西
Or in our case, take back what should still be ours.
这个条款真他妈蠢
This clause is so fucking stupid.
啊 你是怕我们其中一个会取代你爸爸的位置 是吗？
Ah, you're afraid one of us is going to take Daddy's place, eh?
谁知道呢
You never know.
勒德莫斯夫人可能会赢
Mrs. Le DeMoss could win.
因此 正如丹福斯女士所说 这其实全是好消息
So, as Ms. Danforth said, this is all actually good news.
勒贝尔先生向你展示了笑颜
Mr. LeBail has smiled upon thee.
赞美撒旦
Hail Satan.
你
Do you...
你有什么问题吗？
have any questions?
我有
I have
能给我一支烟吗？
Can I have a cigarette?
不
No.
你妹妹的出现真是个意外
Your sister's existence was quite a surprise.
你告诉勒多马斯家族你没有家人 然而 费丝在这里
You told the Le Domas that you had no family, and yet, here is faith.
格蕾丝和费丝 他妈的爱尔兰天主教名字
Grace and faith, fucking Irish Catholics.
【译注: 格蕾丝英语意为赞美 费丝意为信念】
听着
Listen.
咱们赶紧结束吧
We can make this real quick,
因为我他妈的才不要你的席位
because I don't want your fucking chair.
我想我没有说清楚
I suppose I wasn't clear.
至高席位控制议会 议会控制着
The high seat controls the council, and the council controls...
嗯 一切
well, everything.
一切？
Everything?
整个世界
The world.
那又怎样 我就得再抽一张牌之类的吗？
So what, I just have to pull another card or something?
没有那个必要
That won't be necessary.
把它想成双倍或全输的赌局吧
Think of this as double or nothing.
因为你从勒多马斯家族的捉迷藏游戏中
Because you survived Le Domas' game of
幸存下来 你将再次玩那个游戏
hide and seek, you will play that game again.
才不要
No!
这次 是和议会成员一起
This time, with the council members.
他妈的小屁孩
Fucking baby shit bun.
所以 我怎么赢？
So for me to win the seat?
活到天亮
Survive until dawn.
其他人呢？
And the rest of them?
这部分你很熟悉
This part will be familiar.
他们将会杀死你
They will try to kill you.
谁杀了你 赢得至高位
Whoever does, wins the seat.
现在 我们必须在天亮前填补这个空缺
Now, we must fill the seat by dawn,
否则勒贝尔先生就会...
or Mr. LeBail will be...
非常不高兴
very upset.
- 获胜者将... - 太棒了
- The winner will... - Ah! Fuck yeah!
臭孩子
You silly.
赞美撒旦
Hail Satan.
获胜者将在黑神庙
The winner will be coronated in
举行的特别仪式上加冕
a special ceremony in the Black Temple.
勒贝尔先生最虔诚的信徒们
The crème de la crème of Mr. LeBail's
将悉数到场
faithful will be in attendance.
就这些
That's the whole thing.
我不玩
I'm not playing.
哦 对不起
Oh, I'm sorry.
还有一件事
That's the other thing.
我不玩
I'M NOT PLAYING!
你必须参赛
You have to compete.
我还是不玩
I'm still not playing.
好吧
Okay.
普鲁内拉 杀了那个妹妹
Prunella, kill the sister.
不 不 不
NO! NO! NO!
操你妈的
FUCK!
别伤害她
DON'T HURT HER!
你可以把这个拿掉
You can take that off.
听着
Listen!
你们看起来都是好人
You guys seem like good people!
而且我甚至都不知道自己为什么会在这里
And I don't even know why I'm here!
我们大概有七年没见过了
We haven't seen each other in, like, seven years!
为什么不见面？
Why not?
这很复杂
It's complicated.
好手段啊 蠢货
Nice leverage, moron.
她根本不在乎那个女的
This thing doesn't even care about the other thing.
你们两个合不来？
You two don't get along?
我们闹翻了
We had a falling out.
因为什么？
About what?
就因为她是个混蛋
Just her being an asshole.
听着 让我总结一下
Look, allow me to wrap up.
游戏将在下午2点31分准时开始
The game will begin at exactly 2:31 p.m.
为遵守拉贝尔先生所指定的确切时间...
In observance of the exact time Mr.LaBelle...
爸爸
Daddy!
（西班牙语）我的宝贝
Mi amor.
嗯 天呐 你来了
Well, holy shit, here you are.
好吧
Okay.
弗朗西丝卡·埃尔卡多 你个蠢荡妇
Francesca El Caído, you dumb slut.
好吧
Okay.
亚历克斯的前未婚妻
Alex's ex-fiancee.
我的戒指他妈在哪 婊子？
Where the fuck is my ring, bitch?
在你偷走他之前 他买给我的
He bought it for me before you stole him.
就在他爆炸之前 我把它扔向了他
I threw it at him right before he exploded.
你不过是个冷血的婊子
You're nothing but a cold-hearted whore.
要知道 亚历克斯并不傻 但他确实他妈的太好骗了
You see, Alex wasn't stupid, but he sure was fucking gullible.
你毁了我的生活
You ruined my life.
而我他妈都不知道你是谁
And I don't even know who the fuck you are.
别生气 别生气
Okay, No, no, no.
女士们先生们 我们应该行动了
Ladies and gentlemen, we should get moving.
佩妮拉
Pernilla.
等等
Wait.
我想动手
I want to do it.
不 不 不
No, no, no.
我想
I want to...
我只是想让你知道 会是我抓住你
I just want you to know it's going to be me who gets you.
- 懂吗？ - 不 不 不
- Okay? - No, no, no.
不
No!
不 不 不 我只是紧急联系人
No, no, no, I just an Emergency Contact!
理事会成员必须使用一种
The council members must use a weapon that existed
在其祖先与勒贝尔先生达成协议的时期内
during the period in which their ancestor...
就已存在的武器
..made his or her bargain with Mr.LeBail.
议会成员不得互相残杀
The council members are not allowed to kill each other.
如果他们这样做了 即使是意外 勒贝尔先生也会生气
If they do, even by accident, Mr. LeBail will be angry.
而那家有罪之人的整个家族都将受到惩罚
And the offending family's entire bloodline will be punished.
除此之外 百无禁忌
Beyond that, anything goes.
我不想用血笔
I... I don't want to use the blood pen.
你至少可以把它消毒一下吧
Or can you at least sterilize it.
该死
Fuck's sake.
家族成员可以从俱乐部房间观察过程
The families may observe the proceedings from the club room.
万一有猎人不幸身亡
In the unlikely event that any of the hunters should perish,
该家族继承序列中的下一位成员
the next person in that family's line
必须立即接替其位置 投入战斗
of succession must take their place on the field.
祝你们好运
Best of luck to you all.
你不换衣服吗 兄弟？
Aren't you going to change, bro?
为什么？
Why?
我们谁都不需要出去
None of us are going to have to go out there.
切斯特从孩子们刚会走路起就开始训练他们
Chester trained his kids since they could walk
以防这一天真的到来
in case this day ever came.
五分钟内就会结束
This will be over in five minutes.
那里
There.
最好是这样
It better be.
我一小时后有个按摩
I got a massage in an hour.
这位女孩将从第九洞果岭开始比赛
The girl will begin the game on the ninth hole green.
猎手们 就位
Hunters, take your places.
游戏马上开始 十
The game will begin in ten,
九 八 七
nine, eight, seven,
六 五 四
six, five, four,
三 二 一
three, two, one.
没钥匙怎么开
There are no fucking keys.
哦 我是不是忘记给你们钥匙了？
Oh, did I forget to put the keys in there?
操 你作弊
Fuck. Cheaters!
开车
Go!
- 白痴 - 这群傻瓜
- Idiots - Spoof you, Suckers.
费丝
Faith
嗯
Yeah
费丝 快起来
Faith, wake up!
求你了 停下
Please, stop it.
快起来
Come on.
我们得起来 我们得赶紧走
We gotta get up. We gotta move.
妈的
Shit!
我们得起来
We gotta get up.
操
Shit!
Fuck!
我了个天呐
Oh, God!
他们来了
They're coming!
为什么他们想伤害我？
Why do they want to hurt me?
他们根本不在乎你
They don't give a shit about you.
你在这儿只会拖我后腿
You're here to slow me down.
如果你不按照我说的做 我们将会死
If you don't do exactly what I say, we are going to die.
你明白了吗？
Do you understand?
所以我们夺回那个席位后 显然得共享
So we obviously share the seat when we get it back,
但戒指该谁戴？
but who gets to wear the ring?
嗯 爸爸希望由我来负责 所以...
Well, Dad wanted me to be the one in charge, so...
放屁
Bullshit.
他和我说过
He told me.
嗯 他告诉我
Well, he told me.
我来戴戒指
It should be me.
不 他没有说过
No, he didn't.
我们需要去树林里
We're gonna get to the woods.
We're gonna go to the woods.
等等 等等
Wait, wait, wait.
如果有人在树林里等着我们怎么办？
What if there's people waiting for us in the fucking woods?
停下
Stop.
这没什么好争论的
It's not a debate.
我说的算
I am in charge.
哦 你说的算？
Oh, you're in charge?
我之所以在这里 全都是你他妈的错
It's your fucking fault I'm here.
我只是忘了把你从我的紧急联系人名单里移除
All I did was forget to remove you as my emergency contact.
七年了
It's been seven years.
你不认识其他人吗？
You don't know anybody else.
好吧
Fine.
谁杀了她 谁就能戴戒指
Whoever kills her gets to wear the ring.
我不同意
I'm not agreeing to that.
那他妈是什么
What the fuck is that?
我去
God!
哦 妈的
Oh, shit.
那是什么
What is that?
哇 等等
Whoa, hold on.
听着 我是万晨星
Listen. This is Wan Chenxing.
我们之前见过
We met earlier.
哇 等等
Whoa, hold on.
有一个脱离这一切的方法
There's a way out of this.
我让律师仔细查阅了章程 结果发现了一个漏洞
I had my lawyers scour the bylaws and we found a loophole.
我们所要做的就是...
All we have to do is...
哦 天呐
Oh, my God!
打得好
Nice shot.
她在那
There she is.
抓住她
Get her.
哦 天呐
Oh, my God.
该死的
God damn it.
斯基皮 打开屏幕
Skippy, screens.
他们本不该离开果岭的
They weren't supposed to make it off the green.
把那破玩意儿给我
Give me the fucking thing.
该死的
God damn it.
我们没有办法过去
There's no way we're getting over that.
应该会有树可以爬的
There's gotta be a tree we could climb.
哦 我们带着手铐爬树
Oh, we're gonna climb with handcuffs?
好吧
Okay.
好吧 好吧 操
Okay, okay, fuck.
好吧 打开它
Okay, turn it on.
这他妈是什么？
What the fuck is this?
不 只需按输入1
No, just press input one.
对 不 没错
Yeah, no, it's right.
告诉我那个该死的输入1
Show me fucking input one.
点击“开始” 然后点击“菜单” 再点击
Go, press menu, and then go.
你们他妈真是蠢透了
My, you're stupid fucking idiots.
她们再他妈哪儿？
Where the fuck are they?
格蕾丝 我们跑了好久了
Grace, we've been running forever!
操 嗷 操
Fuck, ow, fuck!
你能慢点嘛？
Can you just slow down, please?
哦 对不起
Oh, I'm sorry.
好吧
Okay.
我不敢相信你把我卷入到这破事中
I can't believe you dragged me into this shit.
这是怎么发生的？
How does this even happen?
你是说你不知道你老公信邪教？
You're telling me you didn't know your fiancé was in a devil cult?
这似乎很难不注意到
Seems kind of hard to miss.
我猜你大概只顾着数钱了
I mean, your attention must have been on all that money.
什么？
What?
你什么意思？
What does that mean?
没什么 我只是说我的钱都是自己挣的
Nothing, I'm just saying that I work for my shit,
我不需要靠有钱人来解决我的问题
and I don't need some rich dick to solve my problems.
去你的
Fuck you.
- 去你的 - 去你的
- Fuck you. - Fuck you.
好吧 德里克是做什么的
Okay, what does Derek do?
金融
Finance.
哦 那是我在追有钱人？
Oh, and I'm chasing Rich Dick?
我们刚认识的时候 他还是个穷演员
He was a starving actor when we first met.
饿肚子的演员 还有金融硕士学位？
Starving actor with a fallback MBA?
你以为我是编造了德里克这个人的吗？
You think I made up Derek?
现在有点 对
Kinda now, yeah.
你觉得我可悲
You think I'm pathetic.
你就是见不得我混出头 而你没有
You just can't handle it that I made it and you didn't.
格蕾丝
Grace?
躲起来没用
There's no use in hiding.
我知道你觉得我们是坏人
I know you think we're the bad guys here.
但是没有好人坏人
But there are no good guys or bad guys.
只是体制就是这样的
There's just the system.
不知你是否意识到了
Whether you realize it or not...
你也是这个体制的一部分
you're a part of it, too.
你也是其中的一分子
You contribute to it.
你在助长它
How you enable it.
我并不比你们更邪恶
I'm no more evil than you are.
我们不过是某个远比我们宏大的东西的一颗螺丝钉
We just a small part of something that is much bigger than us.
我们能行 我们能行 我们能行 我们能行
We can do it, we can do it, we can do it, we can do it.
带着点尊严去死
And die with a little dignity.
手铐
Handcuffs!
快跑
Go, go, go! Run, run, run!
起来
Get up.
你真行
Oh my God.
你可别搞砸了
You cannot fuck up like that.
要让我们对爸爸所做的一切有意义
The only way to make what we did to dad mean
唯一的办法就是把那个该死的席位夺回来
something is to win that fucking seat back.
泰特斯
Titus!
你明白吗？
Do you understand?
这是唯一的方式
That is the only way it matters.
让我们去那座楼找个电话
Let's go to that building and look for a phone.
我们在这待得越久 被发现的可能性就越大
The longer we're on this property, the better there are chances of finding us.
我们要找方法离开这
We need to figure out a way to get out of here.
翻过那个墙
Over that wall.
我们直接冲过去
Let's just make a run for it.
那会完全暴露
It's completely exposed.
你太鲁莽了
You are too impulsive.
你从不考虑周全
You never think things through.
你看 他们也没地方躲
Look, they don't have anywhere to hide either.
你会害死我们俩的
You're gonna get us both killed.
（西班牙语）现在轮到我了
Y ahora me toca, toca a mí.
（西班牙语）丹福斯一家被我搞定了
A los Danforth ya los jodí.
（西班牙语）你觉得你能赢吗？妹子
¿Qué vas a ganar, tía?
（西班牙语）想的美
¡Ni eso ni pollos en vinagre!
（西班牙语）操白痴
Joder, gilipollas.
这太冒险了
It's too risky.
行 好吧 让我先好好想想
Just, okay, just let me think this through.
有时候 你得冒一次险
Sometimes you gotta take a risk.
那是枪声吗？
Is that gunfire?
（西班牙语）终于 终于 终于
Por fin, ya, ya, ya, por fin
哦 找到他了
Oh, found him.
谁他妈在射她们
Who's fucking shooting them?
你爸真他妈是个废物
Your dad fucking sucks.
他妈的
Shit.
他从不练习
He never practices.
别让她跑了
If she gets away, I swear to fucking God.
（她们在第三洞的球道上）
你确定你要这么干吗？
Are you sure you want to do that?
我只是
I was just...
操
Oh Fuck!
他射的越来越准了
He's getting better.
别他妈的冒险了
No more fucking risk!
我有个主意
I have an idea.
（西班牙语）操
¡Joder!
（西班牙语）现在轮到我了
Ahora que sí que me toca a mí
（西班牙语）搞什么鬼？
¿Qué diablos es?
（西班牙语）妈的 妈的 妈的
¡Mierda, mierda, mierda!
（西班牙语）操
¡Coño!
哦我的天呐
Oh my God!
走 走 走 走
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go!
混蛋
Fucker!
哦我的天呐
Oh my God!
别看 别看
Don't look at it, don't look at it!
不 不 不 不 不
No, no, no, no, no.
（西班牙语）命真硬啊
¡De esta libré
你还好吗？
Okay？
好吧
Okay
（西班牙语）狗娘养的
¡Hijo de la gran puta!
操
Fuck!
好
Okay.
好 我们找到个电话
Okay. We've got to find a phone.
血都流下来了
You're leaving a trail of blood behind.
我们需要坐下来
We need to sit down.
快点
Come on.
坐在这
Sit here.
坐下
Sit.
操
Fuck.
哦
Oh.
好的 先从小的拔
Alright, let's do the little one.
一
One.
二
Two.
三
Three.
看着我
Just focus on me.
准备好了吗？
Ready?
好家伙 你现在还兼职当护士？
Okay, what are you, a part-time nurse too?
或许是吧
I don't know, maybe I am.
你毕业后干什么了
So, what did you do after you graduated?
哦
Oh.
我 呃...我没读完
I, um, I didn't finish.
我不得不退学
I had to drop out.
真的？
Seriously?
是啊 然后我去端盘子
Yeah, then I waited tables.
说了那么多“追随梦想”的大道理 结果就是这？
After all that follow your dreams shit?
是啊 有时候梦想就是实现不了
Yeah, well sometimes dreams don't work out.
然后我遇到了亚历克斯
And then I met Alex.
那个梦想也没实现
And that dream didn't work out either.
好吧
Okay.
会有点疼
It's gonna burn.
好了
All right.
你知道吗 我找过你
I tried to find you, you know.
我想邀请你参加婚礼
I wanted to invite you to a wedding.
我不会来的
I wouldn't have come.
我知道你不会来 但我想让你知道
I know, but I wanted you to know
我是真心想邀请你的
that I wanted you there.
嗯 你绝对没法让我穿上那些
Well, there's no fucking way you would have got me
丑得要死的伴娘裙 所以
in one of those ugly-ass bridesmaids' dresses, so...
好了 好了
Alright, alright.
喝点？
Shot for the pain?
耶
Yeah.
虽然没什么能减轻跟你在一起的痛苦
Although nothing's gonna numb the pain of being with you.
为了活到黎明
To surviving till dawn.
再一次
Again.
快点 这边
Come on, this way!
听着 我们...
Okay, we're gonna need...
我们得跟他正面硬刚 我们能对付他
we're gonna have to fight him. we can take it.
打他吗？
Fight him?
我们必须这么做
We gonna do.
好吧 我们能行的
It's okay. We can take it.
打架的时候 我们一直是彼此的后盾
We've always had each other's backs in the fight.
好吗？
Okay?
我们能做到的
We can do this.
声音太大了
That's gonna make a lot of waves.
没机会了
We don't have choice.
别乱动
You hold still.
你才别动
你们无处可藏了
You can't hide!
操
Fuck!
老天 要是换我上 她早就死透了
Oh my God, if it was me out there, she'd be dead.
是啊 当然是你了
Yes, of course, it'd be you.
快点 快点 快点
Come on, come on, come on.
走
Go!
抓住那个婊子
Get that bitch!
你
You!
我们需要一些酒杯 因为我们要干杯了
We are gonna need some glasses, cause we're about to have a toast.
哈 哈 哈 哈 哈
Ha ha ha ha ha!
- 别跑 - 不 不 不 不 不
- No. - No, no, no, no!
这他妈是什么？
What the fuck?
沐浴时间
Bath time!
（高温蒸洗）
哦 不 嘿 嘿 嘿
No, no, hey, hey, hey!
啊
Ah!
你要干什么？
What are you doing?
他可能会有手机
He might have a phone.
天呐
Jesus!
操
Fuck!
我的天
Oh god!
妈的
Shit!
好吧 好吧 天呐
Okay, Okay, God.
你能帮我吗 求你了
Can you help me, please?
不 你自己可以的
No, you got this.
你做的很好
You're doing great.
我就不行
I'm not.
我只会碍事
I'll just get in the way.
哦 看
Oh, look!
你做到了
You did it!
我谢谢你啊
Thanks for your help.
他死了
He's gone.
对你的损失我很抱歉
I'm so sorry for your loss.
拉詹先生
Mr. Rajan?
他死了
He's gone.
拉詹先生 令兄既已仙逝
Mr. Rajan, as your brother has left this mortal plane,
您可以上场了
you may take the field.
我必须上场吗？
Do I have to?
在所有继承审判中 您的家庭必须由最年长的成员
Your family must be represented by the eldest member
或依法指定的家主代表
or legally appointed head of household in all trials of succession.
根据第2条第3款C项
Per Article 2, Section 3, Subsection C.
若不从 则意味着失去勒贝尔先生的庇护
Failure to do so would mean forfeiture of Mr. LeBail's favor.
- 你是说... - 恐怕是的
- You mean, um... - I'm afraid so.
我的老婆怎么样？
What about my wife?
你是要放弃拉詹家族族长的身份吗？
Are you saying you want to abdicate your status as head of the Rajan family?
并且让我老婆狩猎
And make my wife hunt?
是的
Yes.
（克罗地亚语）操你妈的
Jebem ti mater da ti jebem.
（克罗地亚语）操你祖宗十八代
I u pičku maternu i u sto pičke materne.
（克罗地亚语）你个畜生
Gade jedan gade!
（克罗地亚语）咒你不得好死
Crko da bog da!
混蛋
Motherfucker!
请您在上面签个名
I'll just need you to sign that.
马杜 如果你签那个
Madhu, if you sign that...
我会让你死得很惨
I will make you very dead.
我也不想这样做
This is hard for me too.
不管了
Fuck it.
好吧 没问题
Okey dokey.
请吧 女士
Ma'am, if you please.
好的 没问题
Okey dokey.
911 你有什么紧急情况
911, what's your emergency?
我需要帮助 我和我姐姐正在被...
I need help, my sister and I are being...
我们现在在丹福斯赌场
We're at the Danforth Casino,
高尔夫球场 或者说那个综合设施里
golf course, whatever, compound.
有人要杀我们
People are trying to kill us.
抱歉女士 您能说慢点 并重复一下吗？
I'm sorry ma'am, could you slow down and repeat yourself?
我决定监控大院内所有外拨电话
I decided to capture all the outgoing calls on the compound
以防他们设法弄到电话
just in case they managed to get their hands on a phone.
怎么做的？
How?
我们拥有这家电话公司
We own the phone company.
而且他们全都是崇拜魔鬼的人
And they're all devil worshippers.
我知道听起来很荒唐 但我们真的需要帮助
I know it sounds insane, but we need help.
我们现在在丹福斯度假村 请派人过来
We're at the Danforth Resort, please send someone.
好的 我知道了
Yes, I understand.
我们会立即派人过去帮忙
We will send help right away.
你能赶到正门吗？
Can you make it to the main gate?
好的 我们会过去的
Yeah, we'll be there.
好的
Ok.
你相信吗？
Are you sure about this?
是的 我确信
Yeah, I'm sure.
我不会伤害你的
I'm not here to hurt you.
你听到了吗 费丝
Do you hear that Faith?
那个拿剑的女人不是来伤害我们的
The lady with the sword isn't here to hurt us.
对的
Right.
我可不想跟你打打杀杀
I have no desire to get into some punchy, kicky situation with you.
有办法解决这个问题
There's a way out of this.
我不是来杀你的
I'm not here to kill you.
我来这
I'm here...
提出个交易
to offer you a deal.
好吧 怎么说
Alright, what is it?
我让我的律师仔细查阅了章程
I had my lawyers scour the bylaws.
我认为其他成员不知道这个
I don't think the other council members know this,
如果你嫁给一个议会成员
but if you marry into a high council family,
如果你嫁给我儿子 我们得到席位 而你也能活下去
if you marry my son, we get the seat and you get to live.
胡说
Bullshit!
我向拉贝尔先生发誓
I swear to Mr. LaBelle.
她同意
She says yes.
不会再狩猎了
No more Hunt.
听着 我知道你第一段婚姻结局不太好
And look, I know your first marriage didn't end well.
但我儿子承福不像亚历克斯
But my Cheng-Fu isn't like Alex.
虽然他是个傻子 但是他很善良
He's an idiot, but he's kind.
如果丹福斯家族不再在幕后操控 世界会好得多
And the world will be far better off without the Danforths pulling the strings.
格蕾丝
Grace.
泰特斯是个变态疯子
Titus is a psychopath.
他姐姐控制不了他
His sister won't be able to control him.
世界会比现在更快走向末日
And the world will go to hell faster than it already is.
但你是个好人
But you're a good person.
当然不是
Of course not.
但这只是程度上的差别罢了
But it's a matter of degrees.
好吧 那我就这么嫁给了一个陌生人
Right, okay, so I'm just married to some stranger.
- 对 但是 - 太好了
- Yes, but... - Great!
你们不必像夫妻一样生活
You don't have to live as a couple.
你可以做任何你想做的事
You can do whatever you want.
对 她会做的
Yeah, she'll do it.
不
No.
什么？
What?
不...这也太容易了吧
No, this seems too easy.
我什么都不用做吗？
What, I wouldn't have to do anything?
好吧...
Well...
好吧 她必须做什么
Okay, well, what would she have to do?
严格来说 她算是组织的一员
Technically, she'd be part of the organization, but
但她只需要做我们大家都要做的那些常规工作
she'd just have to do the usual stuff we all have to do.
- 不算太糟 - 那是什么？
- It's not so bad. - What's that?
那些常规工作？
What's the usual stuff?
- 我是说... - 你是说要献祭山羊 猪之类的？
- I mean... - You mean sacrificing goats and shit and pigs?
他妈的杀害无辜的人？
Fucking killing innocent people?
出卖他妈的我的灵魂？
Selling my fucking soul?
嗯 那还是算了
Yeah, that's gonna be a no.
（西班牙语）他妈的
Puta madre.
滚开 伊格纳西奥
Fuck off, Ignacio!
你这个该死的怪胎
You fucking weirdo!
你知道你不能杀我
You know you can't kill me!
说同意
Say yes!
现在
Right now!
让开
Move!
如果你不说 我会在他动手之前杀了你
If you don't, I have to kill you before he does!
天呐
Jesus Christ!
我同意了
I'll do it!
我会嫁给你那该死的儿子
I'll marry your fucking son!
晨 快点 让开
Chen! Hurry up! Move!
说 同意 天呐
Say yes, Jesus!
就说 同意
Just say yes!
快说
Just do it!
该死
Yeah!
求你了
Please!
晨
Chen!
她会同意的
She'll do it!
她会嫁给你那该死的儿子
She'll marry your fucking son!
她必须说
She has to say it!
你必须说
You have to say it!
该死的
God damn it!
为什么大家都看着我
Why is everyone looking at me?
好吧...
Okay, well...
我得赶紧弄个新的来
I'll need a fresh one of these, stat.
还有 呃 给我件雨披之类的
And, uh, give me a poncho or something.
谢谢 珍
Thanks, Jen.
对
Yeah.
好的
Okay.
我真的不习惯有人在我面前自爆
I'm really not used to people combusting all over me.
对
Yeah.
不
No.
确实总是让人猝不及防
It's always surprising.
你为什么拒绝了
Why did you say no?
你本可以救我们
You could have saved us.
因为我不想后半辈子都他妈地去杀人
Uh, because I don't want to spend the rest of my life fucking killing people.
好吧
Okay.
那个女人出卖了自己的灵魂
That lady sold her soul.
我不会做同样的事
I'm not gonna sell mine.
我宁可去死 也不要那样活着
I'd rather be dead than live like that.
你想知道为什么我不想冒险吗
You wanna know why I don't take risks?
因为我冒了一次险
It's because the one time... I did.
我去了纽约 结果被耍了 然后
I got fucked and moved to New York and I...
我失去了你
and I lost you.
你没有搬去纽约
You didn't move to New York.
你抛弃了我
You left me.
费丝 现在不是提这事的时候
Faith, we can't do this right now.
你本应该可以带我一起走的
You could have taken me with you.
我当时18岁
I was 18!
那是一次千载难逢的奖学金机会
It was a once-iN - a-lifetime scholarship.
- 你怎么会... - 我们是一个团队
- How do you not... - We were a team.
你本可以成为我的法定监护人
You could have become my legal guardian.
你当时15岁？
You were 15?
我怎么照顾你？
I couldn't take care of you?
我可以帮助付房租
I could have helped with rent.
怎么帮
How?
那里是纽约
It was New York.
你是一个孩子
You were a kid.
对 你的孩子妹妹
Yeah, your kid sister.
我告诉过你
I told you.
我曾有个计划
I had a plan.
我会为我们两个打拼出更好的生活
I was gonna make a better life for both of us.
等我毕业了就把你接过来
I was gonna bring you out once I graduated.
你知道那个年纪 三年有多漫长吗？
Do you know how long three years is at that age?
费丝 你当时还好
Faith, you were okay.
你很安全
You were safe.
格蕾丝...我们的养父母人不坏
Grace... We had decent foster parents.
你有个栖身之所
You had a roof over your head.
格蕾丝
Grace...
你抛弃了我
You left me.
我给你打了好几年电话
I called you for years.
你根本不接
You didn't wanna talk to me!
我那时很生气
I was mad.
你伤透了我的心
It broke my fucking heart.
在你伤透我的心之后
After you broke mine.
你还记得你对我说的最后一句话吗
You remember the last thing you said to me?
我说 求你了 不要走 你说...
I said, please don't go, and you said...
“我必须走”
"I have to.
“没有其他选择”
"There's no other way."
我他妈真的很抱歉
I'm fucking sorry.
我为你感到开心
I'm happy for you.
我为你和你完美的生活感到开心
I'm very happy for you and your perfect life.
德里克这个人是我编的
I made up Derek.
我住在布什维克
I live in Bushwick,
也不是什么自媒体人
and I'm not a social media manager.
你干什么的
What do you do?
我是个迎宾员
I'm a hostess.
严格来说 我是服务员 职级比你高
Technically, as a waitress, I outrank you.
他们说我太好看了 所以让我当迎宾
They made me a hostess because they said I'm so pretty.
是啊 但你拿不到小费
Yeah, but you don't get any tips.
我收到很多小费 因为我真的很漂亮
I get a lot of tips because I'm really pretty.
哈 我不需要小费 因为我那个假男朋友德里克赚大钱
Well, I don't need tips because my fake boyfriend Derek makes bank, so...
对 对 对 对
Right, right, right, right.
上帝保佑德里克
God bless Derek.
我们走吧
Let's go.
他们在哪儿？
Where are they?
妈的 你能接那个电话吗
Shit, can you get that?
可能是她们
It could be them.
- 接 - 我不想接
- Answer it. - I don't want to answer it.
她们不能两次找到同一个911接线员
They can't get the same 911 operator twice.
我他妈说什么
The fuck do I say?
赶紧他妈的接就是了
Just fucking answer it.
911.
你有什么紧急情况
What's your emergency?
我们到了
We're here.
警察在哪儿？
Where are the cops?
你们在哪儿？
Where are you?
我们沿着墙走向正门
We're following a wall to the main gate.
我没看到警车
I don't see a cop car.
警察在附近
The unit is close.
待在大门附近 他们会看见你的
Just wait there at the gate, and they will see you.
你个婊子
You bitch.
料到了吗？
Did you see that?
漂亮
Nice.
所以 我们一听就知道是你的声音 他妈的蠢货
So, we knew it was your voice on the phone, fucking dumbass.
对 白痴
Yeah, idiots.
我们一直在监视你
We've been watching you.
你真行
Good for you.
好吧 嗯 告诉我们怎么开门
All right, well, tell us how to open the gate.
你只能在控制室操作
Well, you can only do that from the control room.
我们如何到那
How do we get there?
对
Yeah.
嗯 你回去 左转
Well, you go back inside, you make a left.
最右侧的那部电梯是唯一一部
The elevator on the far right is the only one
通往地下二层的电梯
that descends to the sub-basement.
右转 进入控制室
You make a right, you go into the control room.
当你进去后
When you're inside...
你自己想办法吧
you fuck yourself.
告诉我们如何打开它
Tell us how to open it.
我不告诉你
I don't feel like it.
告诉我们怎么开门 否则我们杀了你哥哥
Tell us how to open the gate, or we're gonna kill your brother.
随便
Fine.
杀了他
Kill him.
我没在开玩笑
I'm not fucking around.
我也是
Yeah, me neither.
他死了 至高位就是我的了
Him out of the way, the seat's all mine.
真是冷血
Well, that's some cold blooded shit.
那么 谁抛弃了谁？
So, who abandoned who?
嗯？
Hmm?
当年
Back in the day.
闭嘴
Shut up.
你 对吗？
You, right?
你是姐姐
You're older.
她今天一整天都在拖你后腿
She's just been holding you back all day.
你知道她还会再次抛弃你的 对吧？
You know she's gonna leave you again, right?
闭上你的狗嘴
Shut the fuck up!
敢打我
Fucking hit me!
格蕾丝
Grace!
谁啊
Who?
对 对 撞死她
Yes, yes, run her down!
这就是我的婊子
That's my bitch!
别被撞死了
Get out of the road!
什么？
What?!
我想她已经走了 老兄
I think she's leaving, boss.
操
Fuck!
格蕾丝
Grace?!
费丝 快跑
Faith, Go!
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
快走
Get out!
跑
Run!
放弃吧 格蕾丝
Give it up, Grace.
这是最好的结局
This is for the best.
滚吧你
Get the fuck off her!
快点
Come on!
一 二 三 起来
One, two, three, come on!
好吧 好吧
Okay, alright.
哦天呐
Oh my god!
我们要上高尔夫球车
We're gonna get into a golf cart!
快点
Come on!
走 走 走
Let's go. let's go, let's go!
“杀了他”
"Kill him."
“我不在意”
"I don't care."
我是在拖延时间 白痴
I was stalling, you idiot.
我肯定对你做了不少事
I surely did a number on you.
你看...
You look at the...
别他妈把我当小孩子
Stop treating me like I'm a fucking child.
好吧
Okay.
我准备好上场了
I am ready to take the field.
实际上你不被允许上场
You're not allowed to, actually.
你放弃了
You abdicated.
你不再是家族的族长了
You're no longer the head of your family.
而且你的妻子控制着你所有的资产
And your wife controls all of your assets.
即使她选择不参与狩猎 她仍然代表你的家族
Even though she's chosen not to hunt, she still represents your family.
什么
Pardon?
你一无所有
You own nothing.
我想 呃
I think, uh...
我想我需要躺下
I think I need to lie down.
你兄弟的遗骸该送到哪里？
Where shall I send your brother's remains?
送去你妈的屁眼里
To your mother's asshole.
你这混蛋
You fuck.
睡个好觉
Have a nice nap.
操你
Fuck you!
还有你
还有你 你这变态小杂种
And fuck you, you creepy little fuck!
我他妈的恨死你们了
I fucking hate all of you!
你也去死吧
Fuck you too.
好吧
Okay.
你一点都不难过
That's not at all sad.
我准备好了
I'm ready.
给我那该死的笔
Give me the fucking pen.
快点
Come on.
快 跑 跑 跑
Come on, run, run, run.
跟你说了要跑
told you to fucking run.
坐下
Just sit.
让我帮你拔出来
Let me...let me help pull it out.
必须拔出来
It's gotta come out!
我去给你找点止痛的东西
I'm gonna find you something for the pain.
哦
Oh!
要辣椒喷雾吗？
There's pepper spray.
你脑子蠢吗？
You don't think?
你听不懂人话吗？
You don't listen?
所有选项摆在你面前
Out of all the options in front of you,
你偏偏次次都选最蠢的那个
you always manage to pick the dumbest one.
真厉害啊
It's actually impressive.
你怎么每次都能那么蠢的
How do you do it?
我救了你
I saved you.
你本来可以自救的
You could have saved yourself.
你本可以去找救援
You could have gotten help.
我照顾不了我们俩
I can't take care of both of us.
我真的做不到
I can't do it.
哦 都是我的错
Oh, it's all my fault.
我知道 我真是个累赘
And I know. I'm such a burden.
你还真是个孩子
You're a fucking child!
我他妈来这里唯一的原因就是你
The only reason I'm fucking here is because of you,
而现在我他妈要死在这里也是因为你
and now I'm gonna fucking die here because of you!
要不是我 你几小时前就死了
You would have died hours ago if it wasn't for me.
哦 抱歉我没跑掉把你扔下 但这事儿更像你的作风
Oh, I'm sorry I didn't run away and abandon you, but that's more your thing.
我离开是对的
I was right to fucking leave.
我真希望你他妈从没找到我
And I wish you never goddamn found me.
你说得对
You're right.
我应该跑的
I should have run.
祝你好运
Good luck.
滚吧
And fuck off.
费丝 等等
Faith, wait!
嗨 贱人
Hi, cunt.
再见 贱人
Bye, cunt.
操
Fuck.
真的？
Really?
操你妈
Fuck.
又一个人了
All alone again?
哈？
Huh?
以为你能搞我
Thought you could fuck with me.
你姐姐呢
Where's your sister?
她走了
She's gone!
她现在正在带警察过来
She's probably bringing the cops right now!
我们掌管着警察
We own the cops.
该死
Goddammit!
你他妈在哪儿 婊子？
Where the fuck are you, whore?
♪ 转身来 ♪
♪ Turn around ♪
我要把你撕碎
I'm gonna tear you apart!
♪ 偶尔我会孤单 心头猛地沉甸甸 ♪
♪ Every now and then, I get a little bit lonely ♪
♪ 你却总不会再出现 ♪
♪ And you're never coming 'round ♪
♪ 转身来 ♪
♪ Turn around ♪
♪ 偶尔我会疲惫 ♪
♪ Every now and then, I get a little bit tired ♪
♪ 厌倦听自己哭声回旋 ♪
♪ Of listening to the sound of my tears ♪
（西班牙语）你个臭婊子
¡Hija de puta!
♪ 转身来 ♪
♪ Turn around ♪
♪ 偶尔我会紧张 ♪
♪ Every now and then, I get a little bit nervous ♪
♪ 怕光阴里最好的年华溜远 ♪
♪ That the best of all the years have gone by ♪
♪ 转身来... ♪
♪ Turn around... ♪
拖累你姐姐 是你这辈子做过的
Slowing your sister down is the only significant
也是你以后唯一能做到的有意义的事
thing you've ever done and will ever do.
你连个人都算不上
You're not even a person.
只是一堆器官和
It's just a collection of organs and...
加上一堆毫无意义的想法...勉强拼凑成个人形
meaningless opinions... approximating a person.
♪ ...但又看见你眼里的光芒 ♪
♪ ...And then I see the look in your eyes ♪
♪ 转身来 睁开眼 ♪
♪ Turn around, bright eyes ♪
♪ 偶尔我会崩溃 四分五裂 ♪
♪ Every now and then, I fall apart ♪
♪ 转身来 睁开眼 ♪
♪ Turn around, bright eyes ♪
♪ 偶尔我会崩溃 四分五裂 ♪
♪ Every now and then, I fall apart ♪
♪ 我今晚多想你 ♪
♪ And I need you now tonight ♪
♪ 此刻比任何时候都更需要你 ♪
♪ And I need you more than ever ♪
♪ 只要你紧紧抱我一次 ♪
♪ And if you only hold me tight ♪
♪ 我们就能永远相依 ♪
♪ We'll be holding on forever ♪
♪ 我们会把一切修正成对 ♪
♪ And we'll only be making it right ♪
♪ 因为我们不会错 ♪
♪ 'Cause we'll never be wrong ♪
♪ 并肩走到尽头的尽头 ♪
♪ Together, we can take it to the end of the line ♪
♪ 你的爱像影子缠绕我始终 ♪
♪ Your love is like a shadow on me all of the time ♪
♪ 我今晚真的需要你 ♪
♪ I really need you tonight ♪
♪ 永远 就从今晚开始 ♪
♪ Forever's gonna start tonight ♪
我一直期盼着这一刻
I've been dreaming about this moment.
你显然不清楚自己现在在哪
You obviously don't know where you are.
这是我的地盘
This is my house.
而庄家永远都赢
And the house always wins.
这句话你憋多久了？
How long have you been saving that one for?
他妈的混蛋
Fucking douchebag.
这是我母亲的裙子
This was my mother's dress.
她唯一的心愿就是让我幸福
All she ever wanted was for me to be happy.
而亚历克斯让我幸福
And Alex made me happy.
闭嘴
Shut up.
你疯了
You're fucking crazy.
我现在就要杀了你
I'm gonna kill you now.
你偷走了他
You stole him.
你改变了他
You changed him.
姐 他根本不爱你
Dude, he didn't fucking love you.
泰特斯
Titus!
泰特斯 停下
Titus, stop!
泰特斯 你他妈在干什么
Titus, what the fuck are you doing?
我要杀了这女孩
I'm killing this girl!
天呐 泰特斯 我们没时间陪你...
Jesus Christ, Titus, we don't have time...
泰特斯 等等
Titus, wait!
我们可以利用她
We can use her.
费丝
Faith!
格蕾丝 我知道你在外面
Grace, I know you're out there.
我抓到了你妹妹 格蕾丝
I have your sister, Grace.
别担心 她...
Don't you worry, she's doing...
嗯 她还没被揍烂掉
well, she's doing just peachy.
说话
Go on
格蕾丝
Grace?
好啊
Yeah.
如果你在接下来的十分钟内不回到大厅 她就会死
If you don't return to the lobby within the next ten minutes, she dies.
格蕾丝 别管我
Grace, just leave me.
- 格蕾丝 别管我 - 她死后
- Grace, just leave me. - After she's dead,
我会找到你 格蕾丝
I'm gonna find you, Grace,
不管你在哪儿 我都会杀了你
wherever you are, and I'm gonna kill you.
如果你想救你的妹妹
So, if you want to save your sister,
滚到大厅来
get your ass to the lobby.
嘿
Hey.
在我杀了你姐姐后
After I kill your sister...
我和你好好玩玩
...you and I are gonna have more fun.
把她带去小屋
Take her to the lodge.
（安保武器）
回来第二轮了 婊子
Back for round two, bitch!
对
Yeah.
替我向亚历克斯问好
Say hi to Alex for me.
她他妈在这里
She's fucking here.
哦 天呐
Oh, Christ!
帮帮我 你这混蛋
Help me, you fucking turd!
费丝
Faith!
格蕾丝
Grace?
我妹妹在哪儿？
Where's my sister?
我不知道
I don't know.
我不玩了
I'm not playing anymore.
我是个无辜的旁观者
I'm an innocent bystander.
哦 妈的 妈的 妈的
Oh shit, shit, shit!
操
Fuck!
格蕾丝
Grace?
费丝
Faith!
她在哪儿？
Where is she?
我不知道
I...I don't know.
I don't know.
告诉我她在哪儿？
Tell me where she is!
我不...
I don't...
告诉我她在哪儿？
Tell me where she is.
啊!
Ah!
天呐
God!
啊!
Ah!
让我们起舞吧 婊子
Let's dance, puta!
妈的
Shit.
操
Fuck.
费丝 不
Faith, no!
快给我出来格蕾丝
Get out of there, Grace!
格蕾丝
Grace!
操
Fuck you!
那块玻璃虽然有两英寸厚
That glass may be two inches thick, but I can still
但我照样能把你妹妹的脑浆喷得满窗都是
blow your sister's brains all over this window.
格蕾丝
Grace!
你只有三秒钟
You only have three seconds.
- 三... - 别这么做
- Three... - Don't do it!
二...
Two...
别听他的
Don't listen to him!
一...
One...
行 好
Okay! Okay!
停手 停手
Stop! Stop!
我出来 我出来
I'll come out! I'll come out!
不要
No!
格蕾丝
Grace!
不要出来
Don't!
格蕾丝
Grace!
如果你嫁给我 格蕾丝...
If you marry me... Grace!
不要
No!
看着我
Look at me!
我宁可死也不愿让你失去灵魂
I would rather die than you lose your soul!
那个女人说 这一切都有漏洞
That woman, she said there's a loophole to all this.
她说 如果我们结婚...
She said if we get married...
你就能得到席位...
you get your seat...
而我也能活下去
and I get to live.
不知道我们能不能在天亮前把她弄出来
Don't know if we'll be able to get her out before dawn.
去他的
Fuck it.
我接受你的求婚
I accept your proposal.
不
No!
好的
Okay.
好
Okay, Good.
很好
Good.
我得先得到一些保证 这样我才放心
I'm going to need some assurances first so I know
我出来的时候 你可别把我们俩都杀了
you're not just going to kill us both when I come out.
我向你发誓...哦 别向我发誓
I swear to you... Oh, don't swear to me!
他妈的白痴
Fucking shit for brains!
向勒贝尔先生发誓
Swear to Mr. LeBail!
我向勒贝尔先生发誓 不会伤害你或你妹妹
I swear to Mr. LeBail that no harm shall come to you or your sister.
你不能
You can't...
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我会让人把你需要的一切都拿来
I'll have everything you need brought in.
做好准备
Get ready.
参加加冕典礼的宾客已经陆续抵达
The guests are already arriving for coronation.
我想我们不妨干杯庆祝一下
I thought maybe we could have a toast.
我们就要成为一家人了
We're about to become family.
格蕾丝 我从没想伤害你
Grace, I never wanted to hurt you.
但是我必须遵守规则
But I had to follow the rules.
听着 我们时间不多了
Listen, we don't have a lot of time.
所以我就直说了
So I'm just gonna say it.
我害怕
I'm scared.
我哥哥
It's my brother.
我不明白
I didn't understand...
他到底是谁
who he really is.
我花了一辈子
I spent my whole life...
寻找他身上的优点
searching for the good in him.
你知道我找到了什么
You know what I found?
什么都没有
Nothing.
他妈什么也没有
Absolutely fucking nothing.
我以为我能控制住他
I thought I could keep him in check.
但他已经失控了
But he's lost it.
格蕾丝 我需要你的帮助
Grace, I need your help.
我们必须一起努力控制他
We have to try to control him together.
拥有一个席位不见得就是坏事
Having a seat doesn't have to be bad.
想想我们能用那种权力做多少好事
Think about all the good we could do with that power.
但我需要你在我身边
But I need you at my side.
嘿 格蕾丝
Hey, Grace.
你不像我们
You're not like us.
你有希望
You have hope.
我现在没有
I don't now.
是你夺走了它
You took it from me.
我们很擅长这个
We are good at that.
来点姐妹时间
A little girl time.
谢谢你让我看清了你的真面目
Thank you for showing me who you really are.
泰特斯 听我解释...
Titus, it's not a ...
泰特斯 停下
Titus, stop.
你想控制我
You want to control me.
不
No.
你想要所有的权力
You want all the power for yourself.
不
No.
你想
You do.
你就是这么想的
你总是这样
You always do.
泰特斯 停下 求你了
Titus stop, please!
看着我 格蕾丝
Look at me, Grace.
Grace, look at me!
让她看着我
Get her to look at me.
我要你看到这个 格蕾丝
I want you to see this, Grace.
我要你看到这个
I want you to see this.
格蕾丝
Grace!
我要你看到我是谁
I want you to see who I am.
我要你看清楚 我不是一个可以被人掌控的人
I want you to see that I am not a man who can be controlled.
你提到了规则
You mentioned the rules.
规则里没有关于杀害家族成员的内容
There's nothing in the rules about killing a family member.
现在来试试控制我啊
Try to keep me in check now.
试试看
Just try it.
我告诉过你 会是我抓住你
I told you it would be me who got you.
我们祭坛见
I'll see you at the altar.
你不能...这么做
You can't...do this
我必须这么做
I have to.
没有别的办法
There's no other way.
没事的
It's okay.
谢姆·汉普拉
Shem HaMephorash!
我他妈什么都看不见
I can't see shit move.
至高无上的撒旦路西法之名
Nomine satani Lucifer excelsis.
奉我们伟大而永恒的恩主之名
In the name of our great and eternal benefactor,
请现身 赐福予众人
come forth and bestow your blessing upon these.
以撒旦 路西法 巴利尔 利维坦之名
In the names of Satan, Lucifer, Baliel, Leviathan,
现身并作证
come forth and bear witness.
撒旦万岁
Hail Satan.
Hail Satan!
欢迎 各位
Welcome, everyone.
我很高兴有这么多人能来
I'm pleased so many of you could make it.
不仅在这个美好的早晨举行加冕仪式
Not only do we have our coronation this fine morning,
我们还有一场婚礼
we also have a wedding.
我们的福杯满盈
Our cup runneth over.
泰特斯
Titus.
请伸出你的手
Your hand, please.
既然你们的誓言是出于本意 且受撒旦之力所驱使
Your vows being made by intent, by the power of Satan,
我现在宣布你们彼此归属
I now confer the possession of each other upon you.
泰特斯·切斯特·丹福斯
Titus Chester Danforth.
你愿意娶这位女士 并承诺与她共度今生与来世吗？
Do you take this woman, in this world and the next?
哪怕是下地狱的烈火？
Unto the fires of hell?
我愿意
I do.
而你 格蕾丝·伊丽莎白·麦考利·勒多马斯 愿意接受这个男人
And do you, Grace Elizabeth MacCaullay Le Domas, take this man to be yours?
在肉体和精神上 并承诺与他共度今生与来世吗？
In flesh and spirit, in this world and the next?
哪怕是下地狱的烈火？
Unto the fires of hell?
我愿意
I do.
他在地狱中锻造之物 任凭凡人休想拆解
What he hath forged in hell, let no mortal tear asunder.
主啊 我们奉你的名祈求
We ask this in thy name, O Lord.
我现在宣布你们结为夫妻
I now pronounce you man and wife.
你可以亲吻新娘了
You may kiss the bride.
泰特斯·丹福斯 特此授予利贝西亚议会至高席位
Titus Danforth, is hereby granted the high seat of the council of Libecia.
撒旦万岁
Hail Satan.
Hail Satan!
撒旦万岁
- 撒旦万岁 - 撒旦万岁
- Hail Satan! - Hail Satan!
搞什么
What the fuck?
杀死自己的家族成员不违反规则
It's not against the rules to kill a family member.
感谢你的提醒
Thank you for that.
是我抓住了你
It's me who got you.
他妈发生了什么
the fuck is happening?
跪下
Get on your knees!
舍姆·哈姆·法拉什
Shem HaMephorash.
这意味着我可以为所欲为 对吧
This means I can do whatever I want, right?
对的
That is correct.
我可以领导这个组织
I could lead this organization.
我可以改变世界
I could change the world.
因此 作为我担任最高委员会主席后的第一项举措
So as my first act as the head of your high council
我特此宣布将我自己
I hereby remove myself
从这个委员会 以及这整个他妈的组织中移除
from the council and this entire fucking organization!
兄弟 她可以那样做吗
Bro, can she even do that?
出人意料的是 章程对此几乎只字未提
There's surprisingly little language about this in the bylaws,
因为没有人相信会有人愿意主动放弃如此大的权力
since no one believed anyone would ever willingly give away so much power.
好吧 但然后谁得到那个该死的席位
Okay, but then who gets the fucking seat?
黎明前谁戴着戒指就是谁
Whoever's wearing the ring by dawn.
黎明什么时候
When's dawn?
大约三分钟后
In three minutes, give or take.
但只有议会家族还是
But it's just the council families or...
严格来说任何人
Literally anyone.
而你说如果黎明前没人戴戒指 勒贝尔先生会
And you said if no one's wearing the ring by dawn, Mr. LeBail would be...
非常不高兴
Very upset.
去吃屎吧 你们这些近亲繁殖的混蛋
Choke on it, you inbred fucks!
我来了 我的真神
I'm coming, my lord!
舍姆·哈姆·法拉什
Shem HaMephorash!
撒旦万岁
Hail Satan!
操 操 操 操
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck!
哦 哇
Oh, wow!
我会杀了你的
I'll kill you.
操...
Fucking...
总得有人把这一切付之一炬
Someone had to burn it all down.
你很擅长毁掉一切
You are good at destroying things.
你自由了
You're free.
再见
See ya.
拜
Bye.
你好呀
Hi, yeah.
嘿 对 别看那里
Hey, yeah, don't look there.
哎哟
Oops
操 太爽了
Fuck yeah!
我还活着 婊子们
I'm alive, bitches!
我们还活着
We made it!
我了个大草
Holy fucking shit!
我已经脱离了组织 所以才幸免于难
I've renounced my pack, so I've been spared too!
让我们他妈的开派对
Let's fucking party!
天呐
Jesus Christ!
那是谁？
What's that?
咩
Meow.
我们能走了吗
Can we go?
咩
Meow.
好的
Okay.
叫你玩火箭筒
Rocket launcher.
来 我们走
Come on, let's go!
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
I love you too.
我想你了
I missed you.
是啊 不过你知道 以后我不必再这么想了
Yeah, well, you know, I'm not gonna have to anymore.
你会他妈烦死我的
You're gonna get really fucking sick of me.
保证？
Promise?
我保证
I do.
你打算怎么处理那只山羊？
What are you gonna do with the goat?
我不知道
I don't know.
你这周打算结几次婚？
How many times are you gonna get married this week?
太快了
It's too soon.
肯定破纪录了
It's gotta be a record.
哦
Oh.
我们要去医院
We're gonna go to the hospital.
我要去洗个澡
I need a bath.
我也感觉快臭了
I stink too.
字幕贡献者
初稿翻译：pubuqi（subhd.tv）
二次校对与听译：Borcolasky（subhd.tv）
终稿校对 听译复核与时间轴：小p（蒙太奇字幕组）